Guide to the David Peck Todd Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Teaching and Lecturing, (1881-1927); Series IV; 1.75 linear feet (4 boxes)
  - New York
    - Correspondence (1):
      - Brooklyn (Institute of Arts and Sciences) (Box 90, Folder 54)
    - correspondence (2):
      - Geneva (Hobart College) (Box 90, Folder 55)
      - New York City (Amherst Association; N. Y. Academy of Sciences) (Box 90, Folder 55)
      - West Point (Academy) (Box 90, Folder 55)
    - Carter, G. C. (West Point)
      See: box 2, folder 40
    - Clippings: Brooklyn, New York City (Box 90, Folder 56)
    - Memorabilia: Brooklyn, New York City (Box 90, Folder 57)
  - Vermont:
    - Correspondence (Box 90, Folder 58)
    - Proctor (University Club; YMCA) (Box 90)
  - Smith, Harold Ladd (Proctor)
    See: box 8, folder 256
  - Washington, D. C.:
    - Correspondence (Box 90, Folder 59)
    - Hall, Prof. Asaph (Washington, D. C.)
      See: box 4, folder 135
    - Clippings (Box 90, Folder 60)
    - Memorabilia (Box 90, Folder 61)
  - Other Clippings (Box 90, Folder 62)
- Post-1922 Correspondence and Papers, (1922-1939); Series V; 4.25 linear feet (12 boxes)
  This series is largely made up of correspondence with friends, family and others on personal and buisness matters following Todd's breakdown in 1922. Since Todd was officially declared incompetent during the period, there is also a considerable correspondence conducted by Millicent Todd Bingham concerning arrangements for his hospitalization and discussions with doctors, attendants and boardinghouse keepers on his progress. Her correspondence on this subject is placed in this series in a chronological arrangement.
  Despite his condition, between 1922 and 1931 Todd carried on negotiotions to produce a silent motion picture, Lawless Men. The titles for this film, correspondence, photographs and publicity material are in this series. He also maintained his scientific and mechanical interests, carrying along a small telescope from place to place. His astronomical observations, designs, inventions and miscellaneous notes are arranged by subject.
  The notes, which he wrote quite steadily in a tiny but legible hand, are uninhibited and sometimes ribald comments on the passing scene. He also wrote poetry, autobiographical reflections and interested himself in world government and get-rich-quick schemes. A portion of the correspondence and printed matter he accumulated in connection with these schemes is arranged chronologically. Since he was a voluminous writer and collector, there is at the end of the series a box of unarranged notes, clippings and memorabilia.
  For other post-1922 correspondence, see the following folders in Series I: Box 3, folder 87; 1923; Box 4, folder 144; 1925; Box 8, folder 268; 1926 Nov 22; Box 8, folder 273; 1968 Sep 26 - Nov 6; Box 8, folder 275; [1926]; Box 8, folder 279; 1925, 1927; Box 11, folder 380; post-1922; and Box 12a, folder 411; 1923 Dec 6 - 1924 Nov 18.
  - A (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - American Book Co. (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - American Journal of Science (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Amherst College (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Amherst College Alumni Association (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Amherst Coll. Class 1875 Reunion, June 1925 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - B (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Bailey, Prentiss, Utica Observer-Dispatch (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Baldwin Locomotive Works (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Bennett, Harold M.: agent, Zeiss (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Borst, Ann Marie (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Brady, Sarah (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - C (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Chesney, E. C. (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Coffin, Forrest; Ida G. (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Collier's (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Columbia Alumni Association (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Crawford, Joseph U. Jessie (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - D (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Dealer, Ted (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Dugan, Raymond S. (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - E (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - F (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Flammarion, Mme. G. C. (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - G (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Georgetown University (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - Glidden (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - Goodspeed's Bookshop (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - H (Box 92, Folder 29)
  - Hagedorn, Hermann (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - Harkness, Mrs. Alma B. (Box 92, Folder 31)
  - Hartness, James (Box 92, Folder 32)
  - Harvard College Observatory (Box 92, Folder 33)
    - Shapley, Harlow
    - Stetson, Harlan
  - Haverford College (Box 92, Folder 34)
  - Heckscher, August (Box 92, Folder 35)
  - Holland, W. J. (Box 92, Folder 36)
  - I (Box 92, Folder 37)
  - J (Box 92, Folder 38)
  - James, A. C. (W. W. Carman, agent) (Box 92, Folder 39)
  - K (Box 92, Folder 40)
  - Kent, Daniel (Box 92, Folder 41)
  - Kunz, George F. (Box 92, Folder 42)
  - L (Box 92, Folder 43)
  - Lodge, Henry C. (Box 92, Folder 44)
  - Losh, C. Leibert (Box 92, Folder 45)
  - M (Box 92, Folder 46)
  - Madison, Mrs. Wilkes (Janet B.) (Box 92, Folder 47)
  - Maxim, Hudson (Box 92, Folder 48)
  - Mecredy, H. E. (Box 92, Folder 49)
  - Moore, J. A. (Box 92, Folder 50)
  - Munson, Frank C. (Box 92, Folder 51)
  - N (Box 92, Folder 52)
  - Navy Dept. (Box 92, Folder 53)
  - N. Y. C. (Mayor Hylan) (Box 92, Folder 54)
  - N. Y. Public Library (Box 92, Folder 55)
  - O (Box 92, Folder 56)
  - Oram, Sarah (Box 92, Folder 57)
  - P-Q (Box 92, Folder 58)
  - Purrington (Box 93, Folder 59)
  - R (Box 93, Folder 60)
  - Rogers, Henry M. (Box 93, Folder 61)
  - Ruder (Box 93, Folder 62)
  - Rusch, Henry A. (Box 93, Folder 63)
  - S (Box 93, Folder 64)
  - Sawyer, Franklin B. (Box 93, Folder 65)
  - Schiff (Box 93, Folder 66)
  - Sesquicentennial Expo, Philadelphia, 1920 (Box 93, Folder 67)
  - Solberg, Thorvald; Library of Congress (Box 93, Folder 68)
  - Spencer Lens Co. (Box 93, Folder 69)
  - State Department (Box 93, Folder 70)
  - Swing (Box 93, Folder 71)
  - T (Box 93, Folder 72)
  - Thomson, Elihu (Box 93, Folder 73)
  - Thursby, Emma Cecilia (Box 93, Folder 74)
  - Tolstoy, Count Ilya (Box 93, Folder 75)
  - U-V (Box 93, Folder 76)
  - W (Box 93, Folder 77)
  - Warner, Worcester Reed (Box 93, Folder 78)
  - Warren, Whitney (Box 93, Folder 79)
  - Warriner, S. D. (Box 93, Folder 80)
  - Washburn, R.M. (Box 93, Folder 81)
  - Welch, John W. (Box 93, Folder 82)
  - Wheelwright, William B. Frances (Box 93, Folder 83)
  - Woodhouse, Henry, Aerial League of America (Box 93, Folder 84)
  - Y-Z; unidentified (Box 93, Folder 85)
  - Mabel Loomis Todd to David Peck Todd
    - 1922-1925 (Box 94, Folder 86)
    - 1926-1932 (Box 94, Folder 87)
  - Millicent Todd Bingham to David Peck Todd
    - 1922-1924 (Box 94, Folder 88)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 94, Folder 89)
    - 1928-1934 (Box 94, Folder 90)
    - 1935-1939 (Box 94, Folder 91)
  - Walter V. Bingham to David P. Todd, 1922-1939 (Box 95, Folder 92)
  - David Peck Todd's letters
    - 1922 (Box 95, Folder 93)
    - 1923 (Box 95, Folder 94)
    - 1924 (Box 95, Folder 95)
    - 1925 (Box 95, Folder 96)
    - 1926 (Box 95, Folder 97)
    - 1927 (Box 95, Folder 98)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 95, Folder 99)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 96, Folder 100)
    - 1933-1939 (Box 96, Folder 101)
  - Bloomingdale Hospital, White Plains, N. Y., July 1922-1923 (Box 96, Folder 102)
  - West Chester, Pa., 1923-1924 (Box 96, Folder 103)
  - Northampton State Hospital, Northampton, Mass., July 1925 (Box 96, Folder 104)
  - McLean Hospital, Waverly, Mass., 1925-1929 (Box 96, Folder 105)
  - Brattleboro Retreat, Br., Vt., 1929-1930 (Box 96, Folder 106)
  - S. Londonderry, Vt., 1930-1932 (Box 96, Folder 107)
  - Hector, N. Y.
    - 1932-1933 (Box 96, Folder 108)
    - 1934-May 1935 (Box 97, Folder 109)
    - June 1935-1936 (Box 97, Folder 110)
  - Madison Heights, Va., 1936-1939 (Box 97, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence re: suggested retreats and hospitals, 1922-1936 (Box 97, Folder 112)
  - Letters to family about David P. Todd after Jun 1922 (Box 97, Folder 113)
  - David P. Todd, motion picture:
    - Promotion, correspondence, 1922 (Box 98, Folder 114)
    - Correspondence:
      - 1933 (Box 98, Folder 115)
      - 1924-1931 (Box 98, Folder 116)
    - Promotion, financing records, accounts (Box 98, Folder 117)
    - Promotion, photographs of advertising circulars (Box 98, Folder 118)
    - Oversize poster for Lawless Men (Box 98, Folder 119)
  - Printed matter collected by David P. Todd (Box 99, Folder 120)
  - Letters to David P. Todd (mostly advertising)
    - 1922-1924 (Box 99, Folder 121)
    - 1925 (Box 99, Folder 122)
    - 1926 (Box 99, Folder 123)
    - 1927 (Box 99, Folder 124)
    - 1928-1935 (Box 99, Folder 125)
  - Scientific notes, 1922-1939 (Box 100, Folder 126)
  - Miscellaneous inventions and ideas, 1925-1932 (Box 100, Folder 127)
  - Miscellaneous notes (1), 1922-1939 (Box 100, Folder 128)
  - Miscellaneous notes (2), 1922-1939 (Box 100, Folder 129)
  - Newspaper clippings collected by David P. Todd, 1922-1939 (Box 100, Folder 130)
  - Letters of congratulation on 80th birthday, 19 March 1935 (Box 101, Folder 131)
  - Letters of condolence to Millicent Todd Bingham on David P. Todd's death, 1 June 1939 (Box 101, Folder 132)
  - Hudson, Charles J., "David Todd: An Appreciation" 1 copy; 2 reprints; letters of comment (Box 101, Folder 133)
  - Biographical sketches (Box 101, Folder 134)
  - David P. Todd death, newspaper clippings, 1 June 1939 (Box 101, Folder 135)
  - David P. Todd death, correspondence re: gravestone, 1 June 1939 (Box 101, Folder 136)
  - Unarranged material: scribblings, printed matter, etc. (Box 102)
- Personal and Financial, (1862-1939); Series VI; 6.5 linear feet (18 boxes)
  This series, which covers the more intimate aspects of Todd's life, begins with his school copybooks of 1867 and goes on with journals, diaries and notebooks to the very last year of his life, 1939. The final notebook is one kept by his nurses recording the circumstances of his death.
  Those interested in domestic architecture and interiors of the turn of the century will find some of the detailed records in the "Financial" section particularly vivid. Included are the specifications for "The Dell," the Todd residence in Amherst from 1888 to 1905, as well as some of the contractor's receipts. The inventory for Observatory House, which the Todds left in 1917, is also included in this section and runs to fifty-two typed pages.
  During the 1960's Millicent Todd Bingham arranged to have a biography of her father written. Two drafts of the manuscript, which was never published, are included in this series in the biographical section as well as extensive notes copied from diaries and letters in the rest of the collection.
  The "Persons" section is devoted to clippings, speeches, and memorabilia concerning friends or associates of the Todds. These items are arranged alphabetically by the name of the person referred to. This section does not contain correspondence.
  The four scrapbooks which make up the last section cover the period 1878 to 1913 and are filled with newspaper clippings, memorabilia, small pamphlets, and some correspondence, largely of a congratulatory nature.
  Scrapbooks:
  1. 1878-1906—Newspaper clippings, memorabilia, correspondence
  2. 1905-1909—Newspaper clippings, memorabilia, correspondence
  3. 1909-1911—Newspaper clippings re: balloon flights and communicating with Mars
  4. 1910-1913—Newspaper clippings, memorabilia, pamphlets, correspondence
  5. 1893-1896—Newpaper clippings, memorabilia, pamphlets, correspondence re: Japan expedition
  6. 1909—Newspaper clippings re: "Signalling Mars"
  *Boxes 111a, 112-114 all contain typewritten, xeroxed or printed material used as research notes by Marguerite Munson in the writing of Eye on the Sky. Many of these items are copies of correspondence from other parts of this collection.
  - Juvenilia:
    - Education:
      - Report cards and merit award, 1865-1868 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - School premiums, 1867 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - School tuition bills (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - School exercise reports: penmanship, [1867-1869] (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - School exercise books: spelling, vocabulary, essays, Latin, Greek, drawing, [1867-1869] (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Greek and Latin in verb book (mss) arithmetic theorems (printed) (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - School compositions, 1867-1870 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - notes and exercises, Latin, etc. (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - Map drawing, [ca. 1869] (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Religious education memorabilia, [ca. 1862-1867] (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - Writings, short stories (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - Columbia College:
        - Greek and Latin notebooks (3) (Box 103, Folder 11)
        - Essays (Box 103, Folder 12)
        - Memoranda and printed manuscripts (Box 104, Folder 13)
      - Diary, 1866 (Box 104, Folder 14)
      - Amherst, astronomy, 1874 January - 1875 July (Box 104, Folder 15)
      - Diaries, 1874-1875 (Box 104, Folder 16)
      - Astronomy notebook: transits, 1874-1875 (Box 104, Folder 17)
      - Lecture notebooks:
        - Burgess on Political Science (Box 104, Folder 18)
        - Hitchcock on Anatomy and Physiology (Box 104, Folder 18)
        - Chart from meteorology (Box 104, Folder 18)
      - Essays (Box 104, Folder 19)
      - Financial memorabilia (Box 104, Folder 20)
      - Printed memorabilia (Box 104, Folder 21)
      - Commencement program, 1875
        - Catalogue, 1874-1875 (Box 104, Folder 22)
        - History of class of 1875 (Box 104, Folder 22)
      - The Olio, 1873 (Box 104, Folder 23)
        - Astronomy notebook 'Index Rerum', 1874 (Box 105, Folder 24)
        - Greek notes (period unknown) (Box 105, Folder 25)
        - Memorabilia: clippings, Circa 1871-1879 (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence:
      - B., E. P. (Box 105, Folder 27)
      - Coffin, Prof. J. H. C., Nautical Almanac (Box 105, Folder 28)
      - Columbia College School of Mines (Box 105, Folder 29)
      - Compton, Sadie (sister-in-law) (Box 105, Folder 30)
      - Newcomb, Prof. Simon (Box 105, Folder 31)
      - Peck, Rev. David (maternal uncle) (Box 105, Folder 32)
      - Peck, Prof. William G. (Box 105, Folder 33)
      - Reeves, Tom (Box 105, Folder 34)
      - Todd, Bertie (cousin) (Box 105, Folder 35)
      - Letterbook, 1878-1881 (Box 106)
  - Financial:
    - Amherst house: "The Dell" specifications; receipts, 1887-1888 (Box 107, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence (Box 107, Folder 37)
    - Observatory House inventory, handwritten, 1918 (Box 107, Folder 38)
    - Observatory House inventory, 2 typed copies, 1918 (Box 107, Folder 39)
    - Contracts (Box 107, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence (Box 107, Folder 41)
    - Insurance policies, correspondence (Box 107, Folder 42)
    - Real estate, 1921-1928 (Box 107, Folder 43)
    - Rhoda Peck Todd, bills and related correspondence, 1898-1901 (Box 107, Folder 44)
    - Estate of Rhoda Peck Todd, correspondence re: final illness, property, 1900-1908 (Box 107, Folder 45)
    - Rhoda Peck Todd newspaper accounts and letters (Box 107, Folder 46)
    - Retirement correspondence, 1916-1920 (Box 107, Folder 47)
      - Printed matter
    - Receipts, 1883-1925 (Box 107, Folder 48)
    - Taxes (Box 107, Folder 49)
    - Banking, 1918, 1937 (Box 107, Folder 49a)
    - Butcher's and grocer's accounts, 1905-1907, 1913 (Box 107, Folder 49a)
  - Diaries and notebooks:
    - Diaries
      - 1876, 1877, 1878 (Box 108, Folder 50)
      - 1886 (Box 108, Folder 51)
    - 2 notebooks, 1891 (Box 108, Folder 52)
    - Brief diary: "Colorado Springs and Pike's Peak", 1893 (Box 108, Folder 53)
    - Pocket notebook, 1893 (Box 108, Folder 54)
    - "Line a Day Diary", 1893, 1894, 1895 (Box 108, Folder 55)
    - Diaries
      The original processor of the David Peck Todd papers included a folder (box 108, folder 56) for Todd's 1907 diary with the following note: "DPT diary 1907, see MLT 1897 diary (reused)." Manuscripts and Archive staff have been unable to locate a David Peck Todd diary for 1907, but believe the note refers to the Bills Payable section of Mabel Loomis Todd's 1897 diary in the Mabel Loomis Todd papers, MS 496C, Series III, box 41, folder 20.
      - 1925, 1926 (Box 108, Folder 57)
      - 1927, 1928 (Box 108, Folder 58)
      - 1929, 1931, 1931 (Box 109, Folder 59)
    - notebooks:
      - 1934-1938 (Box 109, Folder 60)
      - 1936-1938 (Box 109, Folder 61)
      - Nurses' notebook, 1939 May 11-July 15 (Box 109, Folder 62)
  - Biographical:
    - Genealogy:
      - Correspondence (Box 110, Folder 63)
      - Mss. accounts (Box 110, Folder 64)
      - notes and printed materials (Box 110, Folder 65)
      - Newspaper clippings, memorabilia (Box 110, Folder 66)
    - Autobiographical writings (Box 110, Folder 67)
    - Biographical Sketches:
      - Mss. (Box 110, Folder 68)
      - Mss.—by Mabel Loomis Todd (Box 111, Folder 69)
      - Printed: correspondence (Box 111, Folder 70)
      - Printed (Box 111, Folder 71)
      - Printed: Nelson's Loose-Leaf Encyclopedia, 1924-1925 (Box 111, Folder 72)
      - Printed: by Millicent Todd Bingham (Box 111, Folder 73)
    - Lists of published articles by David P. Todd (Box 111, Folder 74)
    - Lists of valuable scientific books owned by David P. Todd (Box 111, Folder 75)
    - Lists of Memberships (Box 111, Folder 76)
    - David P. Todd Publicity: typed, 1870-1924 (Box 111, Folder 77)
    - David P. Todd Publicity: printed
      - 1870-1899 (Box 111, Folder 78)
      - 1900-1908 (Box 111, Folder 79)
      - 1901-1908 (Box 111, Folder 80)
      - 1909 (Box 111, Folder 81)
      - 1910-1917 (Box 111, Folder 82)
      - 1919 (Box 111, Folder 83)
      - 1920-1935 (Box 111, Folder 84)
    - Ms. of Eye on the Sky by Marguerite Munson(*), 1965 (Box 111a, Folder 85-86)
    - Printed material for Munson biography (Box 112, Folder 86a)
    - Correspondence: Munson—Bingham (Box 112, Folder 87)
    - notes by Millicent Todd Bingham for Munson biography (Box 112, Folder 88)
    - Mabel Loomis Todd diary entries (Box 112, Folder 89)
    - Genealogical (Box 112, Folder 90)
    - Biographies and biographical notes on David P. Todd (Box 112, Folder 91)
    - David P. Todd correspondence (Box 112, Folder 92)
    - Diary entries and other autobiographical writings (Box 112, Folder 93)
    - Juvenilia (Box 112, Folder 94)
    - Writings (Box 113, Folder 95)
    - Life in Washington, 1876 (Box 113, Folder 96)
    - Amherst years, 1881 (Box 113, Folder 97)
    - Amherst Observatory (Box 113, Folder 98)
    - Dickinson Material (Box 113, Folder 99)
    - Lick Observatory, Transit of Venus, 1882 (Box 113, Folder 100)
    - Japan, 1887 (Box 113, Folder 101)
    - African Expedition, 1889
      - David P. Todd letters to family (Box 113, Folder 102-103)
      - Printed material (Box 113, Folder 104)
    - Eclipse—Japan, 1896 (Box 113, Folder 105)
    - Expeditions to Tripoli, 1900, 1905 (Box 114, Folder 106)
    - Singkep, 1901 (Box 114, Folder 107)
    - Mars, Percival Lowell, 1907 (Box 114, Folder 108)
    - Total Eclipses (Box 114, Folder 110)
    - Newspaper clippings re: David P. Todd, 1914 (Box 114, Folder 111)
  - Persons File
    - Legal: Personal honorary degrees and club memberships (Box 115, Folder 112)
    - Club privileges (Box 115, Folder 113)
    - Honorary Degree of Ph. D. from Washington and Jefferson College, 1888 (Box 115, Folder 114)
    - Address Book (Box 115, Folder 115)
    - A (Box 115, Folder 116)
    - Aero Club of America (Box 115, Folder 117)
    - Aero Club of New England
    - Aeronautical Society (Box 115, Folder 118)
    - Amherst Aero Club (Box 115, Folder 119)
      - Robert Welles correspondence with Millicent Todd Bingham re: Amherst Aero Club
    - Amherst College Alumni Association and Council (Box 115, Folder 120)
    - B (Box 115, Folder 121)
    - C (Box 115, Folder 122)
    - Columbia Alumni Association (Box 115A, Folder 123)
    - D - E (Box 115A, Folder 124)
      - Douglass, A. E. (Box 115A, Folder 124)
      - Draper, John W. (Box 115A, Folder 124)
      - Draper, Mrs. Henry (Box 115A, Folder 124)
      - Esty, Thomas C. (Box 115A, Folder 124)
    - F (Box 115A, Folder 125)
      - Flammarion, Camille
        See: box 50-51, folder 357-376
      - Frost, Edwin B.
    - G (Box 115A, Folder 126)
      - Glidden, Mr. and Mrs. Charles J. (Box 115A, Folder 126)
      - Goethals, George W. (Box 115A, Folder 126)
      - Grosvener, Edwin P. (Box 115A, Folder 126)
      - Grosvener, Gilbert H. (Box 115A, Folder 126)
      - Grubb, Thomas (Box 115A, Folder 126)
    - H
      - Hale, George E. (Box 115A, Folder 127)
      - Hall, Professor Asaph (Box 115A, Folder 127)
      - Harris, George (Box 115A, Folder 127)
      - Higginson, T. W. (Box 115A, Folder 127)
      - Hills, Leonard Dwight (Box 115A, Folder 127)
      - Hoar, John (Box 115A, Folder 127)
      - Holden, Edward S. (Box 115A, Folder 127)
      - Holland, Dr. William J.
        See: box 30-31, folder 192-217
      - Howells, W. D. (Box 115A, Folder 127)
      - Hudson, Charles S. (Box 115A, Folder 127)
      - Huggins, Lady M. L.
        See: Mabel Loomis Todd Papers, MS 496C.
    - Head, Franklin L. A Notable Lawsuit (Box 115A, Folder 128)
    - James, Mr. and Mrs. A. C. (Box 116, Folder 129)
    - James, Mr. and Mrs. D. W. (Box 116, Folder 129)
    - K (Box 116, Folder 130)
      - Kennan, George (Box 116, Folder 130)
      - Knipping, E. (Box 116, Folder 130)
    - L (Box 116, Folder 131)
      - Langley, Samuel P. (Box 116, Folder 131)
      - Lowell, Percival (Box 116, Folder 132)
    - Maxim, Hudson (Box 116, Folder 133)
    - Munsterberg, Hugo (Box 116, Folder 134)
    - Newcomb, Prof. and Mrs. Simon and Family (Box 116, Folder 135)
    - P (Box 116, Folder 136)
      - Parker, Sir Gilbert (Box 116, Folder 136)
      - Pickering, Prof. and Mrs. Edward C. (Box 116, Folder 136)
      - Pickering, William H. (Box 116, Folder 136)
      - Pierce, Benjamin (Box 116, Folder 136)
    - R (Box 116, Folder 137)
      - Riker, C. L. (Box 116, Folder 137)
      - Rockwell, John (Box 116, Folder 137)
      - Rotch, A. Lawrence (Box 116, Folder 137)
      - Rusch, Henry A.
        See: box 12, folder 391
    - S (Box 116, Folder 138)
      - Safford, T. H. (Box 116, Folder 138)
      - See, Prof. T. J. J. (Box 116, Folder 138)
      - Seelye, Prof. Julius (Box 116, Folder 138)
      - Serviss, Garrett R. (Box 116, Folder 138)
      - Stearns, George M. (Box 116, Folder 138)
      - Swasey, Ambrose E. (Box 116, Folder 138)
      - Swift, Dr. Lewis (Box 116, Folder 138)
    - T (Box 116, Folder 139)
      - Thoreau, Henry (Box 116, Folder 139)
      - Turner, H. H. (Box 116, Folder 139)
    - Thompson, E. A. (Box 116, Folder 140)
    - W (Box 116, Folder 141)
      - Welles, Robert
        See: box 11, folder 92 See: box 10, folder 343
      - Whiting, Sarah (Box 116, Folder 141)
      - Ward, Henry A. (Box 116, Folder 141)
      - Woodhouse, Henry
        See: box 30, folder 190
    - Young, C. A. (Box 116, Folder 142)
  - Scrapbooks:
    - Scrapbook 1, 1878-1906 (Box 117)
    - Scrapbooks 2 and 3, 1905-1909, 1909-1911 (Box 118)
    - Scrapbook 4, 1910-1913 (Box 119)
    - Scrapbooks 5 and 6, 1893-1896, 1909 (Box 120)